<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts by Liz Carey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thoughts by Liz Carey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Recap: Books I Read</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-recap-books-i-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-recap-books-i-read/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2018 Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of books I read in 2018 in no particular order.
Ratings are out of 5 stars.
 Less (Winner of the Pulitzer Prize): A Novel
By Andrew Sean Greer
⭐️ ⭐️ ⭐️ ⭐️
 How to Change Your Mind
By Michael Pollan
⭐️ ⭐️ ⭐️
I &amp;ldquo;read&amp;rdquo; this one via an audiobook. It was fun to have it narrated by Michael Pollan due to his natural cadence and rhythm in reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Christmas dinner</title>
      <link>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A sign of getting older is when visiting home for the holidays is more stressful than not. With every year that passes, a responsibility gets added to my plate. And with this year, both the metaphorical and literal plate as preparing Christmas dinner became one of the layered responsibilities.
And like all great heroes, I didn’t ask for this responsibility; it was simply bestowed upon me against my will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This website is a work in progress&amp;hellip;just. like. me.
Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll have this up and running with content sooooooon.
 Boredom is the only real tragedy for a writer; everything else is material. ― Andrew Sean Greer, Less
 Bay Area born and raised, I currently work as a User Experience researcher based in San Francisco.
I work in both qualitative and quantitative methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a blog</title>
      <link>/blog/starting-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/starting-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>I finally started a blog!
I first thought about starting a blog 3 years ago. I never went through it because:
I didn’t know where to begin I couldn’t think of any content Laziness  The trick is to set aside a few hours and commit.
If you’re familiar with R, the only resource you need is Yihui Xie’s blogdown book.
Key tips that helped me publish this blog:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>A very work in progress personal website. 🚧 ⚠️ 👷
WELCOME. Thanks for stopping by, hopefully you find something you enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 Liz Carey
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>