<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts by Liz Carey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thoughts by Liz Carey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Christmas with the family</title>
      <link>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-with-the-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-with-the-family/</guid>
      <description>A sign of getting older is when visiting home becomes more stressful, than not. With every year that passes, a responsbility is added and layered to your plate.
Holidays are no longer about about predicting what gifts I’ll receive, but rather headcount and logistics planning, including meal prep.
2018 Carey family Christmas menu:
 Mixed salad Roasted root vegetables (recipe from NYT Cooking) Mashed potatoes Beef tenderloin with horseradish crème fraîche sauce (recipe from Serious Eats ) Apple crisp  Christmas Eve Shopping tips:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This website is a work in progress&amp;hellip;just. like. me.
Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll have this up and running with content sooooooon.
 Boredom is the only real tragedy for a writer; everything else is material. ― Andrew Sean Greer, Less
 Bay Area native, born and raised, I currently work as a User Experience researcher based in San Francisco. I work in both qualitative and quantitative methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a blog</title>
      <link>/blog/starting-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/starting-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>I finally started a blog!
I first thought about starting a blog 3 years ago. I never went through it because:
I didn’t know where to begin I couldn’t think of any content Laziness  The trick is to set aside a few hours and commit.
If you’re familiar with R, the only resource you need is Yihui Xie’s blogdown book.
Here are key tips that helped me publish this blog:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>A very work in progress personal website
WELCOME. Thanks for stopping by, hopefully you find something you enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 Liz Carey
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>