<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Thoughts by Liz Carey</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Thoughts by Liz Carey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Recap: Books I Read</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-recap-books-i-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-recap-books-i-read/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2018 This year, I read x number of books. Below is a rank order of my preferred
Less (Winner of the Pulitzer Prize): A Novel
By Andrew Sean Greer
⭐️ ⭐️ ⭐️ ⭐️
How to Change Your Mind
By Michael Pollan
Call Me by Your Name: A Novel
By André Aciman
Sourdough: A novel
By Robin Sloan
But What if We’re Wrong?: Thinking About the Present As If it Were the Past</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Christmas dinner</title>
      <link>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/reflecting-on-christmas-dinner/</guid>
      <description>A sign of getting older is when visiting home for the holidays is more stressful than not. With every year that passes, a responsibility gets added to my plate. And with this year, both the metaphorical and literal plate as preparing Christmas dinner became one of the layered responsibilities.
And like all great heroes, I didn’t ask for this responsibility; it was simply bestowed upon me against my will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a blog</title>
      <link>/blog/starting-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/starting-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>I finally started a blog!
I first thought about starting a blog 3 years ago. I never went through it because:
I didn’t know where to begin I couldn’t think of any content Laziness  The trick is to set aside a few hours and commit.
If you’re familiar with R, the only resource you need is Yihui Xie’s blogdown book.
Key tips that helped me publish this blog:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>